{
    "id": "81c83e13256e472eb39a98a81a586ce5",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I shall ………………….. him if he …………………… .. to me for his misconduct.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pardon, commits",
                "forgive, apologizes",
                "reprimand, commands"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87253cfbec1f47c987cd7fea8d71a4df"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is natural …………………… a man to make mistakes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ebc474996c147cc9d9dc1cf91d1deb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lions roar, elephants …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bellow",
                "bleat",
                "grunt",
                "trumpet"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "45ec549ebb2645c599ce9be0a4246c5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "If a candidate wants ………………….. as President, he / she must win the majority of votes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elected",
                "to be elected",
                "having elected"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c9e94e2bb2e45e7a21da3134515b8c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words has the same meaning as the word ‘Conversant’?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "familiar",
                "pleasant",
                "ignorant"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37da7b9f779f40a39836a67d5e5526e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plane took ………………….. an hour …………………… its arrival.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "after, of",
                "off, after",
                "of, after",
                "off, on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f83630ce30c44be1bd67a7dc475f0e7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was tired because I ………………… .. the whole day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was working",
                "had worked",
                "had been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43fbfb72c5394d07b610561d13bafa41"
        },
        {
            "question": "Give the plural form of sheep",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Sheep",
                "Sheeps",
                "Sheepes"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec22b67a70714aa5bec75f4682354d56"
        },
        {
            "question": "Maiden speech means ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speech given by a maiden",
                "one’s first speech",
                "one’s last speech"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "612be04a16c44325b0c3eb46886242e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Though she refused first, she ………………….. in the end.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came about",
                "came off",
                "came out",
                "came around"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "b4a8d15102f24a2e8830f920e8e95fa4"
        }
    ]
}